hongkongairport.com 2019-12-26

# Privacy Policy - Hong Kong International Airport

The Airport Authority ("Authority", "we", "our" or "us") attaches great importance in protecting the privacy of a person's personal data and is committed to complying with the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance (the "Ordinance") and observing the relevant codes of practice which may be issued by the Privacy Commissioner for Personal Data from time to time.

## (A) Collection and Use

We collect personal data (such as name, email address, postal address and telephone number) from you when you wish to contact us, whether for the purpose of enquiry, for making an application or for giving any feedback to us. The personal data collected will be used for handling such enquiry, application or feedback and contacting you when we reply to you. If other occasions arise where we will collect personal data from you, we will inform you of the purposes for which they are collected and such personal data collected will only be used for the stated purposes for which they were collected.

## (B) Confidentiality and Disclosure

We will keep any personal data held by us confidential. Such personal data will only be accessed by our authorised personnel for the purposes for which such personal data were collected. No personal data will be disclosed to any unauthorised personnel unless they are required to be disclosed under the laws of Hong Kong.

## (C) Data Security and Retention

We will strive to protect any personal data held by us against unauthorized access or processing. Our web servers are hardened, protected behind "firewalls" and monitored by Intrusion Detection Systems in order to prevent unauthorized access. Practical steps will be taken to ensure that personal data will not be kept longer than necessary and the Authority will comply with all relevant statutory and regulatory requirements concerning the retention of personal data.

## (D) Your access rights

You may make a request to access to your personal data which are held by us. Such access request form can be downloaded from the [website of the Office of the Privacy Commissioner for Personal Data, Hong Kong](https://www.pcpd.org.hk/index.html). You may also request the Authority to correct the personal data that you have accessed if such data are inaccurate. We will handle your request as soon as possible. Please note that under the Ordinance, the Authority has the right to charge a reasonable fee for complying with a data access request. Data access and correction requests can be addressed to us as follows:

## (E) Suggestions

We are committed to protecting privacy in respect of any personal data you provide. If you have any questions about the Authority's Privacy Policy, or our practices in this regard, please contact our General Personal Data Officer by post at the above address.

## (F) Use of Cookies

When you browse this website, cookies will be stored in your computer's hard drive. Such cookies can be retrieved by this website to show the state of your web browser's previous visits to this website. We will not collect any personal data from you under this circumstance. You have a choice not to accept the cookies, but if you do so, certain functionality of this website may not be available.

The Privacy Policy is subject to change from time to time. Any changes made will be posted on this page.
